[Fangs of Fortune]
[Episode 2]
Archivist Wen,
how come you're bleeding again?
I need to go out.
I waited for you so long that I almost fell asleep.
You knew I would come?
I know you can't let it go.
I can't let go of your life.
You have the blood of countless lives on your hands.
Even your death is not enough.
So you were bound to come.
Because you want to know the true way to use the Cloud Light Sword.
I can tell you.
But you have conditions.
Yes.
What do you want?
I want a vow from you.
Make a solemn vow.
Never to go back on your word.
What do you want me
to do?
I want you to kill me.
I'll teach you the true way to use the Cloud Light Sword.
Then...
Kill me.
You really want to die?
Yes.
And I must die by your hand.
I don't understand.
If you want to die,
there are thousands of ways.
Why must I be the one to kill you?
People call me the evilest demon.
Why do you think that is?
It's obviously because you've committed numerous evil deeds.
You're extremely brutal.
Mr. Zhuo, don't believe those rumors.
What?
Don't tell me you're actually a good demon?
No.
I'm more vicious and eviler
than rumors say.
Not only do I absorb the world's malicious energy,
but I'm also a vessel that contains it.
Do you know what malicious energy is?
Of course I do.
It can destroy heaven and earth.
It can make the world
dark and sunless,
and be littered with corpses.
So,
when I die,
a new vessel
will immediately be born in the world
to replace me
and contain and absorb the endless malicious energy.
And that new vessel,
whether good or evil,
righteous or wicked,
is unpredictable.
Your Cloud Light Sword
can dispel all evil spirits and demons.
Dying by your sword
can end the vessels' reincarnation cycle.
I, Zhuo Yichen,
swear to the heavens
that as long as Zhu Yan
teaches me the true use of the Cloud Light Sword,
I will surely slay him with my sword.
If I break this vow,
may heaven and earth destroy me,
and my soul be scattered.
Very good.
What's going on?
What happened?
Well...
I don't know what happened either.
When Commander Zhuo came just now,
he was fine.
Commander Zhuo was here?
He just left.
Open the door.
Yes.
Mr. Fan Ying,
[Demon Hunting Bureau Meeting Hall]
we need to select
an elite force to lead the charge
to quickly solve the Water Ghost's wedding murder case.
This is the list of candidates drafted by the Prime Minister.
Each of them possesses extraordinary skills
and they are unwaveringly loyal.
There are twenty-eight people in total.
Five will suffice.
Quantity over quality
is useless.
I have prepared five tokens.
Two of them have already been handed to them.
[Demon Hunting Bureau]
These two
are not on the Prime Minister's list.
Get up.
Stop pretending.
I didn't expect Ms. Wen Xiao to care so much about me.
I can't help but feel touched.
I'm already up and you still stabbed me?
Just in case.
I'll give you a small cut first.
There's Huanling Powder on the blade.
It can suppress your demonic powers.
Otherwise,
I'm afraid you might hurt me.
You're the one who's been hurting me.
Humans and demons should keep their distance.
Why are you here to see me?
I'm here
to give you a gift.
It seems Mr. Fan Ying has accepted my proposal.
It'll be impolite not to reciprocate.
I'm a very polite person.
Tell me,
what do you want?
I want an answer.
What did
Zhuo come to see you for?
Why do you care so much about him?
He's just an ordinary mortal man.
Zhuo
is no ordinary man.
Zhuo?
Zhuo.
What's going on?
Are you going to tell me or not?
This is an agreement between Commander Zhuo and me.
It's a secret.
How can I easily tell others?
Others?
Mr. Zhao Yuanzhou,
you specifically named me
to hunt demons together.
Now you call me
'others'?
That's right.
You're not happy about
hunting demons with me?
Not happy.
Mortal women
all say one thing and mean another.
You seem to know a lot about mortal women.
I know a thing or two, I suppose.
Don't you also carry a pen and notebook every day
to study us demons of the Wilderness?
You and I,
we're not so different.
How much have you been snooping around about me?
If I hadn't specifically requested it,
I'm afraid with your weak and frail
body that could be blown over by the wind,
you'd never make it into the Demon Hunting Squad in your lifetime.
When did I ever say I wanted to join?
See?
The storybooks were right after all.
Women
always say one thing and mean another.
Before I came here,
I had already inquired about you.
Ms. Wen Xiao is dedicated to helping demons,
secretly releasing demons many times
from under the nose of Chongwu Camp.
You always say
people can be good or bad,
and demons can be righteous or evil,
right?
And haven't you already
eagerly accepted the token?
[[Demon Hunting Bureau]]
Yet you still say you don't want it?
You're so impressive.
You know so much.
I also know
that you're the disciple of the Baize Goddess.
What's so special about that?
All the demons in the Wilderness
know that I'm the new Baize Goddess.
If we're talking about
fame in the Wilderness,
I'm no less famous than you, Zhu Yan.
A goddess without the Baize Token
or Baize Divine Power
is indeed very famous.
A well-known laughingstock.
If your master Zhao Wan'er
saw you as you are today,
would she be disappointed?
I love swinging on a swing the most.
I hate pushing swings the most.
Have we met before or not?
You've already
asked this question once.
Then come closer and look again.
Make sure.
Do you know why your body
is so weak?
Because the Baize Token is missing.
I know.
You don't need to tell me.
Then do you know
that if you can't find it back,
you'll die soon?
It seems your master didn't tell you.
Now,
you have no divine power.
Unless you find the Baize Token,
you'll soon die of weakness.
I can help you.
I came here from the Wilderness
to help you find the Baize Token.
In this situation,
we can cooperate for mutual benefit
and get what we need.
Isn't that good?
I do need the Baize Token.
What about you?
What do you want?
I also want the Baize Token.
What do you want the Baize Token for?
Because the goddess hasn't returned.
If this continues,
the Wilderness will be done for.
After Zhao Wan'er's death,
[One month ago]
the position of Goddess of the Wilderness has been vacant.
Without the protective power,
powerful and brutal demons
break through the Kunlun Gate
and enter the human world.
If Baize doesn't return,
the Wilderness will perish.
Zhu Yan,
the past has already been bid farewell
and old friends have departed.
Don't be a distant boat in the sea of bitterness,
imprisoning yourself.
Find the goddess
and retrieve the Baize Token.
This is
your last chance for redemption.
The water ghost bride abduction case that your adoptive father wants to investigate
also stemmed from this.
I once made a vow
to protect the Wilderness,
bring back the demons who fled from the Wilderness,
and restore peace to the human world.
I'm speaking so passionately.
What's with your expression?
Your acting is so fake.
Tone it down a bit.
Okay.
Everyone knows
that when Zhu Yan appears,
chaos will erupt.
Eight years ago, you massacred the Demon Hunting Bureau,
killing countless people.
Among them
were Zhuo's father and brother.
You
are full of malicious energy
and brimming with evil.
You don't seem like a demon with such a
sense of responsibility
and justice.
Is that so?
Is that what everyone thinks?
If even you think this way...
Yes.
Then I can only cooperate with the Chongwu Camp.
Your words can't threaten me.
You can't threaten me either.
Let's just stay at this impasse.
One word:
wait.
I won't fall into the same trap twice.
You think I'd let you get close to me again?
How about this then?
No matter what evil intentions you harbor,
your purpose for coming to the Demon Hunting Bureau
was to find me.
If I die,
your plans will all fail.
Move.
Whoever I want to die
cannot possibly live.
Conversely,
those I want to live
cannot possibly die in front of me.
Live well.
At least,
your master hopes you live well.
Sir,
Mr. Fan has sent three tokens.
[Demon Hunting Bureau]
Once you select the final two people,
I will issue the official document
to announce the completion of the Demon Hunting Bureau's reconstruction.
[Demon Hunting Bureau]
Pei Sijing.
[Pei Sijing]
[Bai Jiu]
Bai Jiu!
[Jixin Clinic]
Take this to get the medicine.
The first elite vanguard squad will depart immediately
to replace the Chongwu Camp
and take over the water ghost bride abduction case.
I specially brought pastries from Qingfeng Restaurant.
They're your favorite, Zhuo.
[Demon Hunting Bureau]
Do you really have to join the Demon Hunting Bureau's vanguard squad?
Isn't it good?
Of course not.
The demons are vicious
and it's too dangerous.
With you here,
what do I have to fear?
You'll protect me.
I will definitely protect you.
It's just that...
For many years,
we have been searching for the Baize Token.
We worked for so long
but have no clues.
Now that Zhu Yan has appeared,
and is willing to help,
it is a great opportunity.
Do you believe him?
He's the evilest demon.
Of course I don't trust him.
But I always feel
he seems like an old friend of my master.
Can't you give me a push?
No.
How old are you now?
I can't swing just because I've grown up?
Master told you
to take care of me.
If it's him,
he might really know the whereabouts of the Baize Token.
Impossible.
Zhu Yan killed so many people from the Demon Hunting Bureau back then.
Your master is the Baize Goddess.
How could she possibly be old friends with Zhu Yan?
You're so young.
Don't always have such a precocious expression.
I'll be 24 next month.
Even if you were 42, I'd still be your aunt.
I...
I know.
You can't get over that hurdle in your heart.
He's the one who killed your father and brother,
yet you have to fight alongside him
and interact with him every day.
I'm letting down the spirits of my father and brother.
But to protect the Demon Hunting Bureau,
you still agreed, didn't you?
This is your ancestral home,
the home you grew up in.
You were willing to donate it
to rebuild the Demon Hunting Bureau.
Can't you just...
After my father and brother died,
this place became just an empty, desolate house.
Not a home.
I lived here alone in a daze,
wasting my time.
Eight years ago,
I already lost my home.
Now that the people from the Demon Hunting Bureau are here,
there's more life here.
It's actually better than before.
For generations, the Zhuo family
has been full of people with a sense of righteousness.
Temporarily working with your enemy
for the sake of investigating the case,
for the Baize Token,
they will surely understand you.
They won't blame you.
Actually, I agreed to him
joining the Demon Hunting Squad because...
What?
Mr. Fan.
Zhuo,
do you know that your ancestor, Bingyi,
once destroyed the evil demon Yinglong?
Yes, I know.
Yinglong had the divine power to glimpse the future.
He once predicted
that every successor of Bingyi who inherited the Cloud Light Sword
would slay the evilest demon of their time.
Yinglong's prophecy
seems to be wrong.
I can't kill him.
No.
Yinglong's prophecies have never been wrong.
Because it's not a prophecy.
It's a curse.
Slaying Zhu Yan
is my mission.
If this is also considered a curse,
then I couldn't ask for more.
It's nothing.
Oh, right.
Why did you go to the dungeon alone to see Zhao Yuanzhou?
You and Zhao Yuanzhou...
There's something wrong.
We have a secret.
You
are the one with something wrong.
Hey.
What a coincidence.
You're indeed a monkey.
Although your Demon Hunting Bureau looks poor,
it's quite spacious.
You can work in the front
and live in the back.
Food and lodging are provided too.
Saves me the trouble of finding a place to stay.
How did he get released?
Wasn't a Demon Hunting Squad formed?
I was afraid you'd leave me behind,
so I followed you.
You actually followed me?
Shameless.
Isn't Mr. Zhuo eager to solve the case?
I'm helping everyone save time.
Isn't that good?
How many are we still missing?
We're still missing two.
As it happens, they are
the two types of people I'm worst at dealing with.
Which two types?
One is a woman.
The other is a child.
Leave it to me.
[Jixin Clinic]
Thirteen years old?
He probably can't even reach my knee, right?
Is he capable?
I don't want to find another one who'll hold us back.
Another?
Explain yourself.
She's getting agitated.
Although he's young,
he's a renowned miracle doctor in the capital and beyond.
He can diagnose not only humans,
but also demons.
Oh.
Come back.
You have signs of life,
but according to the Huangzhong technique, your pulse level should be at nine.
Why is yours only at one?
Unless...
You're not human?
Your medical skills are indeed impressive.
You!
You... Get out of my way!
This silver needle of mine is very powerful.
It can slay demons and exorcise evil spirits.
[Demon Hunting Bureau]
He's gone.
Demon Hunting Bureau's token?
Little Bai Jiu,
I know
you don't want to.
But
-If I tell you...
-Who said I don’t want to?
I'm so happy!
I've really been chosen!
Mom,
I've made it!
Again!
Come on.
Who are you?
What did you do to them?
Ms. Pei,
I'm from the Demon Hunting Bureau.
I'm Wen Xiao.
Interested in a chat?
No.
Wake them up quickly,
or don't blame me for being impolite.
What are you doing?
I've never seen such an absurd assassin as you.
Ms. Pei,
one month ago
at the foot of Kunlun Mountain,
a demon massacred a village.
You were ordered to eliminate the demon.
It should have been a merit worthy of reward,
but because of this case,
you were deeply affected
and lost your military position.
In Chongwu Camp,
rumors spread.
You investigated me.
You've always been unable to find closure,
because
you couldn't be certain
whether what you killed with your own hands
was truly a demon
or a human.
That's right.
That's why I resigned from my official position.
It was to avoid getting involved in demonic affairs again.
Don't you want to clear up your confusion?
I've investigated
but found nothing.
We all
can help you.
You all?
Break.
Us.
But mainly me.
She
can't be relied upon.
If I couldn't find anything,
what makes you think you can?
Isn't it obvious enough?
I'm a demon.
Things that humans don't know,
I know.
About your brother's matter,
I know that too.
[Demon Hunting Bureau]
Since we're here...
It's the Spring Festival.
[Demon Hunting Bureau]
Open.
So this is the Demon Hunting Bureau?
I wonder if I'll see him
after I go in.
Kid,
who do you want to see?
Why is it you again?
How come
you walk without making any sound?
Stop dawdling.
Just go in already.
You don't understand.
Haven't you heard?
Inside the Demon Hunting Bureau, there's
a thousand-year-old demon
with a green face and fangs.
It's ugly in appearance,
and it even eats people.
Nonsense!
How could it possibly be ugly?
It's true!
I saw it with my own eyes.
At that time,
many experts from the Demon Hunting Bureau fell to the ground,
leaving only me.
I was terrified then,
but I still bravely went up
and fought fiercely with that Zhu Yan.
In the end, I can only say
it was a narrow victory.
Otherwise, why do you think the Demon Hunting Bureau would choose me
to join the first elite squad?
Bai Jiu.
Hello.
Don't look down on me because of my short stature.
That's because I'm only 13 years old.
Don't underestimate me because of my young age.
I'm very capable.
Since Commander Zhuo chose you,
it means
you must have some exceptional qualities.
Mr. Zhuo chose me?
The hero I admire chose me.
Let's go.
I'll take you to meet Mr. Zhuo.
Thank you.
You're so kind.
What's wrong with you, Great Demon?
Why are you so late?
Great Demon?
Where?
Him.
Great Demon.
Zhu Yan.
So you're the Great Demon Zhu Yan?
Let me go.
Put me down!
You don't need to be so afraid.
Zhao Yuanzhou
is just unserious.
He likes to scare people.
He doesn't eat children.
Isn't he that
extremely hungry demon?
If he's so hungry,
how can he resist eating people?
He must be Mr. Zhuo Yichen.
The thing in his hand
is the legendary
Cloud Light Sword of the Bingyi Clan.
Aren't all demons afraid of this sword?
Even Great Demons must fear it, right?
Hello.
Ms. Pei,
you're here.
Let me introduce you.
This is the new doctor,
Bai Jiu.
Hello, Sister.
Please take good care of me from now on.
Fully draw the bow.
♫An arrow in the hand♫
Steady your breath.
♫A string in the heart♫
Hello, Sister.
♫A backside standing, turning into forever♫
From now on,
please take good care of me.
♫The moon shines on the south♫
♫But I look north♫
♫I only hope the snow comes a bit later♫
Don't misunderstand.
I'm not here to join you.
I'm here to return this token.
I don't believe the words of an
extremely evil demon.
It's right not to believe him.
People from the Demon Hunting Bureau,
come out.
♫Heartlessness births a dream♫
♫The dawn stings without hesitation♫
♫The world and universe sing for me♫
♫Spring, summer, autumn, winter; everything becomes nothing♫
♫Heartlessness births a dream♫
Mr. Zhuo, you're so imposing and powerful now.
I'm afraid you've forgotten the pain once the wound has healed.
Back then, the Demon Hunting Bureau was destroyed by Zhu Yan.
It was the Chongwu Camp that took on the dangerous mission
and protected the people.
What?
You forgot?
The Chongwu Camp is ruthless and vicious
in demon hunting.
You even harm innocent lives.
It goes against the law.
The Chongwu Camp should have been stopped from acting arbitrarily long ago.
Demons are inherently violent.
To eliminate future troubles,
it's better to kill a wrong one than to let one go.
The Chongwu Camp privately built an underground black market,
trading demon beast furs and bones,
making exorbitant profits.
And in the name of demon hunting,
you forcibly recruit able-bodied men
and occupy civilian homes.
Does King Xiang know about all of this?
Mr. Zhen Mei,
we're in broad daylight
and in full view of everyone,
You're not planning to commit murder and arson, are you?
The Demon Hunting Bureau has fallen into disrepair.
The weather is hot and dry,
which caused a wildfire.
What does that have to do with me?
Have you asked my permission
before burning down the Demon Hunting Bureau?
What do you think you are?
Demon.
Demon?
Then you deserve to die even more.
Reverse.
I forgot to tell you,
I'm the type of demon
that likes to kill people to vent my anger.
Zhao Yuanzhou,
calm down.
Mr. Fan.
Spare them.
General Wu,
what brings you here?
Mr. Fan said he prepared a gift for King Xiang.
I came personally to receive it
on behalf of King Xiang.
Over the past eight years,
close to 700 innocent people have been killed by the Chongwu Camp
while hunting demons.
The list and related evidence are all here.
Please review them, General.
I accept this
grand gift on behalf of King Xiang.
He now understands
the Demon Hunting Bureau's determination to revitalize itself.
He agrees for you to take over from the Chongwu Camp
and thoroughly investigate the Water Ghost murder case.
The Demon Hunting Bureau hereby requests permission from King Xiang
to thoroughly investigate the Water Ghost murder case.
Do not harm civilians.
Do not be negligent or lazy.
The Demon Hunting Bureau should spare no effort
to solve this case.
I'll trouble you all
to sign and stamp this,
so I can take it back
and report back to King Xiang.
[Military Order]
Sir,
you can press down at the end of the scroll.
Mr. Zhuo,
there are people behind you, right?
There's one more person.
She won't need to.
I just heard her say
she refuses to join the Demon Hunting Bureau.
The Demon Hunting Bureau is truly useless.
Even the dogs that our Chongwu Camp doesn't want
look down on the Demon Hunting Bureau.
[Military Order]
Did you hear any dogs barking?
It's a bit noisy.
They're finally gone.
Indeed.
It's a pity the evidence of Chongwu Camp's crimes was burned.
The real evidence
was secretly sent
to the Prime Minister the day before.
If one day they really need to be held accountable,
the Prime Minister will make the decision.
The chance to investigate
the Water Ghost case didn't come easy.
Whether the Demon Hunting Bureau can be revitalized
depends on this crucial battle.
Zhao Yuanzhou,
you'd better not play any tricks.
Mr. Zhuo,
trust me.
Keep dreaming.
These are all the files on the Water Ghost case.
Everyone, please take a look first.
[Military Order]
Sir,
you can press down at the end of the scroll.
[Military Order]
[If the case isn't solved within 5 days, it will be viewed as a misdemeanor and those who signed will apologize with suicide]
[The Demon Hunting Bureau vows to crack the case within 5 days. I hereby make a pledge.]
This is not ink.
This is blood.
The blood of the demon Meng Ji.